A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Virginia Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1974-2006.
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence and subject files of the Virginia Superintendent of Public Instruction (Accession 39607), 1974-2006., Extent: xx boxes. (Box 1-xx)
  - Correspondence and subject files (Dr. S. John Davis), 1983-1984.
    - Instructional Media and Technology, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - Instructional Media and Technology Development, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - Technology - Utilizationa and Evaluation, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - School Libraries and Textbooks, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - Special Compensatory Education, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - ECIA Chapter I, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - Migrant Education, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - Special Education - Administration and Finance, 1983-1984. (Box 31b)
    - Special Education - Programs and Pupil Personnel Services, 1983-1984. (Box 31b)
    - Special Education - Pupil Personnel Services, 1983-1984. (Box 31b)
    - Special Programs - Gifted, 1983-1984. (Box 31b)
    - Vocational and Adult Education, 1983-1984. (Box 31b)
    - Adult and Contintuing Education, 1983-1984. (Box 31b)
    - Adult Education, 1983-1984. (Box 31b)
    - Comprehensive Employment and Training Service, 1983-1984. (Box 31b)
    - Proprietary School Service, 1983-1984. (Box 31b)
    - Vocational Program Services, 1983-1984. (Box 31b)
    - Agricultural Education, 1983-1984. (Box 31b)
    - Business Education, 1983-1984. (Box 31b)
    - PEPS Project - People, Equipment, Procedures and Systems / Implementing Techniques of the Electronic Office, 1983-1984. (Box 31b)
    - Distributive Education, 1983-1984. (Box 31b)
    - Home Economic Education, 1983-1984. (Box 31b)
    - Trade and Industrial Education, 1983-1984. (Box 31b)
    - Associate Superintendent of Financial and Administrative Services, 1983-1984. (Box 31b)
    - Financial and Administrative Services - Budget Director, 1983-1984. (Box 31b)
    - Financial and Administrative Services - Accounting and Finance Director, 1983-1984. (Box 31b)
    - Financial and Administrative Services - Pupil Transportation, 1983-1984. (Box 31b)
    - Financial and Administrative Services - Energy and Facilities, 1983-1984. (Box 31b)
    - Financial and Administrative Services - School Food Service, 1983-1984. (Box 31b)
  - Correspondence and subject files (Dr. S. John Davis), 1984-1985.
    - A - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - American Association of School Administrators (AASA), 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Annual Conference of Division Superintendents, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Appalachia Educational Labs, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Accomack County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Albemarle County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Alexandria, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Allghany / Highlands County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Amelia County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Amherst County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Appomattox County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Arlington County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Augusta County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - B - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Bath County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Bedford City, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Bedford County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Bland County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Botetourt County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Bristol, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Brunswick County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Buchanan County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Buckingham County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Buena Vista, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - C - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Certificates of Appointment, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Colleges and Universities - Virginia, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Colleges and Universities - Out of state, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Community Colleges - Virginia, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Campbell County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Cape Charles, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Carroll County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Charles City County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Charlotte County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Charlottesville, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Chesapeake, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Chesterfield County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Clarke County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Colonial Beach, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Colonial Heights, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Covington, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Craig County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Culpeper County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - D - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Developmental Disabilities Protection and Advocacy Office, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Durrette for Governor, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Danville, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Dickenson County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Dinwiddie County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - E - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Education Commission of the States, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Educational Testing Service, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Educational Equality Project, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Executive Agreement, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - Executive Committee - NTE Policy Council meeting, 1984 Nov. (Box 32a)
    - Executive Committee - NTE Policy Council meeting, 1985 May. (Box 32a)
    - Essex County, 1984-1985. (Box 32a)
    - F - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Fairfax County, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Falls Church, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Floyd County, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Fluvanna County, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Franklin City, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Franklin County, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Frederick County, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Fredericksburg, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Fries, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - G - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - General Assembly - House of Delegates, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - General Assembly - Senate, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - General Assembly - Other states, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Galax, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Giles County, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Gloucester County, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Grayson County, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Greene County, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Greensville County, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - H - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Halifax County, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Hampton, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Hanover County, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Harrisonburg, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Henrico County, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Henry County, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Highland County, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Hopewell, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - I - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - J - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Jobs for Virginia Graduates, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - James City County, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - K - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - Keep Virginia Beautiful, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - King and Queen County, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - King William County, 1984-1985. (Box 32b)
    - L - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Links, Inc., 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Lancaster County, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Lee County, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Lexington, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Loudoun County, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Louisa County, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Lunenburg County, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Lynchburg, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - M - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Madison County, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Manassas, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Manassas Park, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Martinsville, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Mathews County, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Mecklenburg County, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Middlesex County, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Montgomery County, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - N - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - National Association of Secondary School Principals, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - National Association of State Boards of Education, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - National Commission on Excellence in Education, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - National Teacher Examinations (NTE) and Policy Council, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - New London Academy, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Non-Public School Accreditation Advisory Committee, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Nelson County, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - New Kent County, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Newport News, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Norfolk, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Northampton County, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Northumberland County, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Norton County, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Nottoway County, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - O - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Orange County, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - P - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Personnel Newsletter - Dept. of Education, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Presidential Scholars Program, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Procurement Act, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Programs mandated by Federal, State or Local Government, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Patrick County, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Petersburg, 1984-1985. (Box 33a)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Portsmouth, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Powhatan County, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Prince Edward County, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Prince George County, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Prince William County, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Pulaski County, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - R - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Rappahannock County, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Richmond City, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Richmond County, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Roanoke City, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Roanoke County, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Rockbridge County, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Rockingham County, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Russell County, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - S - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Secondary School Recognition Program, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Six-Year Plan, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Southeastern Cooperative Education Programs, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - State Advisory Committee for Education of the Gifted, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - State Agency Group Luncheons, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - State Departments of Education - Other states, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - State Ed (newsletter of the Superintendent of Public Instruction), 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - State Special Education Advisory Committee, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Superintendent's Advisory Council, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Superintendent's Employee Advisory Committee, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Superintendent's Study Groups, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Salem, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Scott County, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Shenandoah County, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Smyth County, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Southampton County, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Stafford County, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Staunton, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Suffolk, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Surry County, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - Sussex County, 1984-1985. (Box 33b)
    - T - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - Tazewell County, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - U - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - United States Congress, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - United States Dept. of Agriculture, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - United States Dept. of Education, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - United States Dept. of Education - Block grants / Chapter II, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - United States Dept. of Education - Office of Civil Rights, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - United States Dept. of Education - Office of Special Education, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - United State Environment Protection Agency - Asbestos, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - United States Savings Bond Campaign, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - United States Secretary of Education, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - United Way Campaign, 1983-1984. (Box 34a)
    - United Way Campaign, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - V - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - Varina High School - Governor's Center for Educational Innovation and Technology, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - Virginia Association for Children with Learning Disabilities (VACLD), 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - Virginia Association for Education of the Gifted, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - Virginia Association of Elementary School Principas (VAESP), 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - Virginia Association of Independent Schools, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - Virginia Association of Independent Special Education Facilities, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - Virginia Association of Private Career Schools, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - Virginia Association of School Administrators (VASA), 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - Virginia Association of Secondary School Principals, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - Virginia Community College System, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - Virginia Congress of Parents and Teachers, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - Virginia Council on Economic Education, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - Virginia Council for Private Education / Non-Public School Advisory Committee, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - Virginia Council of School Administrators, 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - Virginia Education Association (VEA), 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - Virginia High School League (VHSL), 1984-1985. (Box 34a)
    - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind (Hampton/Staunton), 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind - Hampton, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind - Staunton, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - Virginia School Boards Association, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - Virginia State Advisory Council on Vocational Education, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - Virginia State Library, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - Virginia Beach, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - W - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - Warren County, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - Washington County, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - Waynesboro, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - West Point, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - Westmoreland County, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - Williamsburg, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - Winchester, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - Wise County, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - Wythe County, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - X - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - Y - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - York County, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - Z - Correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - S. John Davis - Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - S. John Davis - Virginia Tech Press Release, 1984 Aug. (Box 34b)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (General), 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (Virginia Association of Counties), 1984 Aug 20. (Box 34b)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (Leadership Style / Wintergreen Retreat), 1984 Sept 15. (Box 34b)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (VASA / VSBA Joint Annual Convention), 1984 Oct 3-5. (Box 34b)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (Retirement of Dr. Andrew Wright / Carlton Webb - Stafford Co.), 1985 Jan 13. (Box 34b)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (Orientation on 2 plus 2 Program to prepare master technicians), 1985 Mar 7. (Box 34b)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (Tenth Annual Conference on Gifted and Talented Education, 1985 Mar 9. (Box 34b)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (Thomas Dale High School presentation of academic awards), 1985 Apr 10. (Box 34b)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (Creative Leadership - Region VIII Secondary School Principals), 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (Annual Superintendents Conference), 1985 Apr 28-30. (Box 34b)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (Roast for William J. Burkholder retirement), 1985 May 18. (Box 34b)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (Fairfax Education Association - Electives Teacher Forum), 1985 May 16. (Box 34b)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (Rural School Effectiveness Workshop), 1985 June 25. (Box 34b)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - S. John Davis - Governor's Job Training Coordinating Council, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - S. John Davis - Governor's Employment and Training Council, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - S. John Davis - Governor's Advisory Committee on Child Abuse, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - S. John Davis - State Water Plan Advisory Committee, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - Special Assistant Public Information, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - Administrative Director - Board/Staff Relations, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - Block Grant - Chapter II, 1984-1985. (Box 34b)
    - Deputy Superintendent, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Association of School Administrators conference, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Institute of Government - UVA, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Administrative Director - Planning and Evaluation, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Division Administrative Review, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Director - Division of Management Information Services, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Data utilization and reporting, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Administrative Director - Personnel and Professional Development, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Director - Division of Research Evaluation and Testing, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Special Assistant for Policy and Program Planning, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Associate Director of Testing, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Associate Director of Innovative Planning, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Assistant Supervisor of Research and Evaluation, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Supervisor of School Evaluation, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Beginning Teacher Assistance Program, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Master Teacher Plan and Career Ladder / Pay for Performance, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Division of Technical Assistance - Special Assistant, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Teacher Education / Certification, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Personnel - Positions, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Project Discovery / Dropout Prevention Pilot Program, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Director - Personnel and Employee Relations, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Division of Professional Development, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Associate Superintendent for Curriculum and Instruction, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Administrative Director - Office of Virginia Schools for the Deaf and Blind, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Community Education, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - General Education, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Magnet School - Science and Technology, 1984-1985. (Box 35a)
    - Governor's Conference on Education, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - electronice Classroom, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Varina High School - Governor's Center for Educational Inovation and Technology, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Sciences and Elementary Administration, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Elementary Administration, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Entrance age, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Health, Physical Education and Driver Education, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Mathematics, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Science, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Secondary Administration, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Languages, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Social Studies, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Fine Arts, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Instructional Media and Technology, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - School Libraries and Textbooks, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Film / Television Production and Audiovisual Equipment, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Special and Compensatory Education, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Special Education Complaints, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - ECIA - Chapter 1, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Special Education - Administration and Finance, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Special Education Programs and Pupil Personnel Services, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Pupil Guidance Services, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Hoffman Booklets - Educational Opportunities in Virginia, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Special Education Programs for Handicapped, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Special Programs - Gifted, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Vocational and Adult Education, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Audit and Continuing Education, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Abstract and Abstract Supplement: A Secondary and Post Secondary Program to Prepare Technicians, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Adult Education, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Comprehensive Employment and Training Service, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Proprietary School Service, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)
    - Veterans' Training, 1984-1985. (Box 35b)